Harrison Maloney

About Me

I am currently a student working part time with a passion for a wide range of music and the processes the go into creating it. In my spare time I like to create music both digitally in a DAW and physically with my home studio setup, which is comprised of a Juno 6, DX7, 909, 303, MPC 1000 as well as a 3630 compressor and SPX90 effects unit. I am also currently teaching myself piano and guitar.

Skills

- Knowledge of multiple DAW such as Logic, Pro Tools and FL Studio
- Experience with hardware synths, drum machines, samplers and rack units
- Knowledge of signal flow in a home setting and studio setting
- Knowledge of microphone techniques
- Knowledge of industry plugins such as those from FabFilter and Universal Audio

Previous Work Experience

TESCO COLLEAGUE, OCT 2021-PRESENT

I work in all departments, filling shelves, working checkouts, helping customers, bringing deliveries and during the summer running the warehouse on my own due to a retirement and 2 injuries as well as training new members of staff.

PAPER ROUND, AUG 2019-JAN 2022

Delivering newspapers to houses all over the town no matter the weather and through the Covid pandemic.

REPUBLIC OF MUNCHERY, JUL 2023-SEP 2023

Helping my dad at his job by packing orders and pallets of dog food to meet pickup deadlines.

Education

HNC SOUND PRODUCTION - PERTH UHI, 2024-PRESENT

I am currently studying HNC Sound Production at Perth UHI and I am planning to continue on to the Audio Engineering degree.

ABERTAY UNIVERSITY, AUG 2023-JUN 2024

I completed the first year of the Computing degree at Abertay before realising that is not what I want to do.

OPEN UNIVERSITY, AUG 2022-JUN 2023

I completed a Physics and Space course from the Open University while in sixth year at High School.

Contact

- hpm1809@hotmail.co.uk
- 07484859714

BLAIRGOWRIE HIGH SCHOOL, AUG 2017-JUN 2023

Advanced Highers – English, Biology Highers – Computing, Biology, English, Maths, Chemistry Nat 5s- Computing, Biology, English, Maths, PE, Design and Manufacture, History